Live boldly.
Me Before You is a drama, romance film directed by Thea Sharrock.
Lou Clark, a directionless 26-year-old from the English countryside, takes a job at the local
castle as a caregiver and companion to a wealthy young banker, Will Traynor.
Wheelchair-bound from an accident two years prior, the once adventurous Will has all but
given up — that is until Lou determines to show him that life is worth living.
Louisa 'Lou' Clark, played by Emilia Clarke.
William 'Will' Traynor, played by Sam Claflin.
Camilla Traynor, played by Janet McTeer.
Stephen Traynor, played by Charles Dance.
Bernard Clark, played by Brendan Coyle.
Katrina 'Treena' Clark, played by Jenna Coleman.
Me Before You is a 2016 British romantic drama film directed by Thea Sharrock in her
directorial debut and adapted by author Jojo Moyes from her 2012 novel of the same name.
The film stars Emilia Clarke, Sam Claflin, Janet
McTeer, Charles Dance and Brendan Coyle.
The film was shot in various historic locations across the United Kingdom, including
Pembroke Castle in Wales and Chenies Manor House in Buckinghamshire, England.
Released on 3 June 2016 in the United Kingdom and North America, the film
received mixed reviews and grossed $208 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of depression, small town,
based on novel or book, england, artist.
The tone is emotional.